已经完成了[超距]行动
have completed Operation Out Distance,
所以他们现在都可以协助你们了
so both are now available to assist you.
少尉欧帕卡是这里的高级军官了
Second Lieutenant Opálka is the senior officer here.
是的 这是事实
Yes, this is true,
但你任务的优先级是凌驾于我的军衔之上的
but your mission objective supersedes my rank.
我们收到了伦敦的回话了 [类人猿]行动
We had word from London. Anthropoid.
有最高优先级
Utmost priority.
我们要竭尽全力的协助你们
We assist with everything possible.
这样的话...
So...
就看你们的表演了,兄弟
This is your show, bratři.
那么 我们目前知道海德里希每天
So, we know that Heydrich returns to his family
回到帕内斯克的家里
every day at Panenské Břežany.
但他家里的庄园和办公的堡垒都处于戒备森严的状态
But, both his chateau and the castle are both heavily guarded.